jobsbuddies.com 2015-05-10

# privacy policy-jobsbuddies

**What type of information and details do we collect?**

When you fill out a form on the jobsbuddies.com we take your personal details like name or e-mail address.  
You can also visit Jobsbuddies anonymously. In that case we will not use any personal information.

 **Why do we collect your name or e-mail type of information ?**

We collect your information just to improve our jobsbuddies.com and we also collect your information just as to improve or do our the customer services better.

 **D **o we protect your information?****

Yes we protect your precious information like your personal details and e-mail address and a variety of security measures are implemented to maintain the safety of your very personal details.

We don’t sell your information because we know how somebody feels when his/her personal details are publicized.

 **Do we use cookies?**

The josbbuddies will use the cookies in future . We are not using cookies nowadays because we are not showing any types of advertisement. But may be in future we will use the cookies so as provide you the best and ads related to you . And we will use cookies so as the same type advertisement must not be shown to you repeatedly.Cookies help us to track the advertisement on our jobsbuddies.com .

 **Third party links**

We will just use the third party links which will only help you .They will only for you not for us. We will put the links of the various companies so as you can contact them easily . It will save your time to find a good job which can easily make you happy.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

Jobsbuddies privacy policy applies only to the online privacy policy to the any type of information or your personal collected through the Jobsbuddies website and it is not for the information which is collected offlin by Jobsbuddies.com

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we will make any changes in our privacy policy in future , We will update the Privacy Policy with a notice .

This policy page was last modified on 20th July 2014

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy then you can easily contact us using the information below.

http://jobsbuddies.com/  
Hyderabad

India  
jobs2buddies@gmail.com  
The best and better option for contacting us will be jobbuddies mail id and our contact us page.You can visit our contact us page by this link- http://jobbuddies.com/contact-us
